Juliette Gondon

New Haven, CT

Phone: 860-878-5491 | Email: juliettegondon@gmail.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/juliettegondon/ GitHub: https://github.com/juliettegondon

Portfolio: https://juliettegondon.github.io/portfolioround3/

Summary

Full Stack Web Developer with experience in design, digital content creation, and tech marketing. Delivering smart design solutions to smart people.

Keen on designing aesthetically appealing web interfaces with attention to detail and brand awareness. Skillfully implemented innovative web development concepts in a team setting to more efficiently create full stack projects. Bilingual in English and Spanish. Strong in writing, leadership, communication, and management.

Technical Skills

HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, Node.js, Git, React.js, MongoDB, MySQL & Express. Final Cut Pro, Adobe Photoshop & Lightroom, and keynote.

Projects

Franklin Products Employee Management

https://github.com/Rivenception/P2_Time_Manager | https://intense-badlands-45869.herokuapp.com/

Employee and administrator timesheet and cost management service for engineers at Franklin Products. Run reports for overtime hours and view a user's past timesheet entries, administrative visibility of active projects and tasks completed in real time.

Responsibilities were creating different login routes for different types of employees, and designing the UI while matching the company's pre-existing brand design using handlebars.

E-Volve

https://aithub.com/iulietteaondon/evolve

A online wellness portal that allows users to manage all aspects of their personal health - from fitness, to medical data, to mindfulness and mental health. Created using React.js, this site uses MongoDB to store user information and requires sign-in authentication.

Tasks included designing and creating the MVC for React app, implementing routing with API's, and implementing CRUD database functionality.

Dinner with Developers

https://github.com/mkolek1015/Group-Project-1 | https://mkolek1015.github.io/Group-Project-1/

A dinner planning app which generates wine and food based upon a choice of ingredients and dietary restrictions.

Core responsibilities included webflow, and using HTML, CSS and JQuery to construct and display the outcome of our API calls.

Education

University of Connecticut School of Engineering - Full Stack Web Development Certificate

2020-2021 | 6 month intensive course focused on teaching technical programming skills in HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, JQuery, Bootstrap, Node.js, HTML, CSS, jQuery, React.js, databases, and data structure.

Quinnipiac University, Hamden, CT - Health Science Studies

2016-2020 | Bachelor of Science in Health Science Studies, president and founder of Student Fitness Organization. Senior year thesis focused on global public health with a semester spent in Spain.

Experience

Educator | Iululemon

New Haven, CT | 2019 - present

Educating guests on product, creating experiences and fostering community connections. Lead educator of diversity and inclusion. Working in a team dynamic - recognized by local and regional managers for being adaptable, flexible and eager to learn. Motivated and extroverted team player with proven success in customer service and cross-team collaboration.

Content Creator and Social Media Management | Juliettiful, LLC

New Haven, CT | 2014 – present

Owner & writer of Juliettiful.com. Self-taught in SEO, email marketing, word processing, collaborative work, and budgeting. Privately managing web and social media for multiple clients. Maintaining a personal blog and digital brand including content creation, post planning, and adherence to brand identity to portray blog's image via digital media. Gained 10% revenue growth completely independently from 2019-2020.